Hello friends welcome back to ICC Stock
Market, today we are going to talk about
ICC Lombard General Insurance
and are going to do its stock analysis
for 28th April 2023, so let's go
straight to our chart, here also we have opened this chart,
I opened this chart with my
zero account, if you do
not have your demat account yet, then
I have mentioned it in the description below and now I have
given it from the stock, if you want,
through our link, now you will be able to open your
demat account in the stock absolutely free
and from there you will be able to start your trading
journey, so let's talk, first of all
what will happen today in General Insurance, so
here as you can see, today
we have seen
4.82% negative closing in the stock, 1076 closing is being
seen, so is there going to be a
similar negative moment in the coming two
or is there going to be a positive moment, we will
talk about it later, along with this
what is your support for tomorrow here, John and  The
resistance that is formed in the stock will definitely be
marked and we will tell you and here on the
basis of today's closing what do we think can happen
in the stock tomorrow,
so let's go to our chart and talk about what we
see in the coming two, what is going to happen, so
here
we have already opened the chart of one day, I will
talk about volume, high volume to
see today, the candle medium is showing a
small decrease on the lower side, the
RSI has reached around 46 which
gives us a signal of a service slide positive moment here, but remember whether it is
RS or any other indicator, we
cannot rely only on the indicator, there are
many factors here which
give momentum to any stock, we must
definitely consider them whenever
we trade in any stock, so now as far as
I am concerned, for both the coming days in these stocks,
my open here is definitely of
negative moment for both the coming days, here the expected
DO side in the stock which is first around
here  If it is seen around 1069 and it is
crossed then a downfall in the stock
can be seen by placing it at 60 and here at 1052, keeping this in mind, the
trade in the rest of the stock is still negative, so
in negative trade I would definitely recommend you to short as much as possible
in intraday
or crop the opportunity
because that is where your right
reward ratio will be in your favor, that is where you will see the property potential, what do you think, what can happen in the coming two, do tell us by commenting, here I will
tell you what is the meaning of short term and long term, for short term if
you ever see the stock in the bank
sustaining above 1106 for two days,
definitely when you look there, from
there you will get an easy
website move of 5 to 10% with 10 to 15 trading
disk,
for the rest of the long term, if I will
not recommend you to buy at the current price, then I will buy the
stock.  By falling easily, the
stock can easily move around here.
Here you will see the
levels here, so here around this level, which
you get here,
definitely below 10:40, when it is a very
good bank for the bank because the long term
level, you do not have to invest 100% capital, invest up to 20 to
25% capital, the remaining capital you keep by
holding, if
you see 10 to 20% capital on additional long, then
do additional bank there, remember additional bank will
help you in reducing your buying average price
and the more you get for the
long term, the better
profit you will get in the long term, if you
need any other investment related help then we have given our WhatsApp number below,
now you can definitely contact us,
let's keep it ready, let's talk in the chat,
what is going to be seen tomorrow,
so here we have already opened the one hour chart,
here on the upper side, the
rope will definitely hit, but on the lower side,
in this range, the stock which ever  When I
came, we did not analyze it, so
whatever marking I am doing here,
you should do it from the back on your chart
because this marking will
help you a lot in maintaining your target and top loss,
so definitely
do the marking from the beginning onwards, otherwise if
you have not subscribed to our channel yet, then
subscribe to our channel right now and also turn on the
bell icon for the notification
because we
bring every day four strokes and analysis for all of you
and here is the next and in the coming two,
what are you going to see in the stock,
here you
try to understand it completely on the basis of what is there, so on the
bottom side we have also marked some psychological
numbers, so
definitely keep that in consideration as well, rest of
our marking is done here, if
I talk about closing here, then the
closing has happened around 1077, our
direct support comes here, our direct support comes at 1069, our
direct region comes at 1078, remember that  The
area from direct support to direct support is
called no trading
India. It means that if you see the stock moving in this range, then
you should not trade here at all. You have to
wait for the
stock to cross on either side and then
take confirmation. If you do not know
what confirmation kindly is, then in the i button, I have given
this video of concept and target study here,
you must watch it.
We have explained everything to you there. Now, if there is
no other matter left, then before opening, it is important for
you to know what are the
direct supports and directors. So,
here the direct
support is of 1050, after that there is
10149, here there is direct
six, after that there is 10902, so
whatever support I have told you here,
you must keep this in consideration and put your trade here. I will tell you about the
closing of the day in my stock for tomorrow, there is
definitely
a positive movement here, from 1078 onwards.
Our closing expectation is in the range of 1080.
What do you think can happen
tomorrow? Please let us
know by commenting. If you liked our license,
please
like and share this video and subscribe to our channel
Na Bhole. Thank you
[Music]